# Neil GOODRIDGE

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

## **ABOUT ME**

I'm a committed learner, having recently completed the highly regarded Le Wagon bootcamp in London in my evening and weekends alongside my full time job. I'm looking forward to transferring the skills I have learned in my current and previous roles, and pairing them with those I've learned at Le Wagon in an engineering role.

I'm currently a Regional Business Manager for Subway's Business Development Office for Greater London, with 10+ years of management experience in the hospitality sector at many levels and companies, all including heading major system changes from scheduling, recruitment and training, to rolling out major regional initiatives such as third-party delivery most recently.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- · Ruby, Ruby on Rails, JavaScript
- HTML, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap
- Databases, SQL and Postgresql
- · Minitest Rails, Yarn package manager
- · Git and Github, API's
- Heroku

#### **PROJECTS**

# The OA

An Online Activism platform built with Ruby on Rails using MVC pattern • Designed DB schema • Wrote majority of front end • Presented to class.

# WaterRnR 🗹

Host your own pool, or rent someone else's in your area. Built using RoR, incorporating TypeScript, jQuery and basic CRUD actions.

#### **EDUCATION**

### Le Wagon - London, Batch #525 (2021)

25-week part time intensive web development bootcamp learning Ruby on Rails, HTML, CSS, JS, Bootstrap, SQL, Heroku and Github...

#### **Hellesdon College**

Economics, Chemistry, Philosophy and Religious Studies.

#### **Hellesdon High School**

10 GCSEs.

# INTERESTS

Home Cinema, Formula 1, Playing guitar, Road cycling, Football, Gardening, Travelling, Cooking.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Subway Business Development Office | 2018 - Regional Business Manager | Greater London

- Leading a team of 9 Business Consultants, responsible for up to 264 stores' operations and profitability at a London-wide level.
- Member of the Third-Party Delivery Steering Group for the UK, tasked with rollout and ongoing improvement of the program.
- Led the London region into third-party delivery in 2018-19 that added an average of 24% to stores P&L and kept them afloat through 2020's lockdowns.
- Put together the main content for three annual conferences and presented this to around 230 people (internal and external).

# Subway Business Development Office | 2016 - 2018 Business Consultant | Greater London

- Regular meetings with stores and franchise owners for brand standards reviews.
- P&L reviews, hands-on training with store teams and owners.
- Researching and submitting potential new locations to HQ.

**Greggs** | 2015 - 2016

# Floating General Manager | London (South East)

- Accountable for P&L for 3 stores in South East London.
- Training of the teams up to 12 per store.
- Turned around Lewisham store from -£5k pw to +£4k in 5 months.
- Implemented online scheduling system.

McDonald's | 2008 - 2015

## **Assistant Manager** | Norwich Airport

- General P&L responsibilities in support of the General Manager.
- Led largest update of McDonald's internal systems for 3 stores.
- Weekly scheduling for up to 115 people.
- Boosted Apprenticeship program completions by 40% YoY.